{
    "subject": "resource/Hardcore_(2015_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/Work/runtime",
    "object": "90.0",
    "human_readable": "The runtime of the film Hardcore (2015) is 90.0.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9245294332504272,
            "question": "What is the runtime of the film Hardcore (2015)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7497096657752991,
            "question": "Compare the runtime of Hardcore (2015) to an average movie."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6699696183204651,
            "question": "Is Hardcore (2015) a short film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6609904766082764,
            "question": "Do you think the runtime of Hardcore (2015) is appropriate for its genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5924265384674072,
            "question": "Would a shorter or longer runtime have impacted Hardcore (2015) differently?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5423707962036133,
            "question": "Would you consider Hardcore (2015) a typical feature film length?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5347390174865723,
            "question": "How long is the movie Hardcore (2015)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.529552698135376,
            "question": "How does the runtime of Hardcore (2015) influence your perception of the story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3342170715332031,
            "question": "For how many minutes does Hardcore (2015) run?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2858377695083618,
            "question": "What is the length of Hardcore (2015) in hours and minutes?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The runtime of the film Hardcore (2015) is 90.0.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1105_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=For how many minutes does Hardcore (2015) run?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1105_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the runtime of Hardcore (2015) influence your perception of the story?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1105_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How long is the movie Hardcore (2015)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1105_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1105_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1105_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1105_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1105_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1105_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1105_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1105_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1105_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1105_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1105_46.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is not explicitly stated, but based on the context, it seems like the query might be related to information about a film, specifically \"Hardcore Henry\" and its characteristics.\n\nQuery: The runtime of the film Hardcore (2015) is 90.0.\n\nGiven the information in the documents:\n\n- file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1105/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt\n- Godzilla Minus One\n  Runtime: 2h 5m\n- file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1105/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt\n- Summation\n- Hardcore Henry gets most of the film wrong because it lacks execution.  But in the fleeting beats where the action connects and the camera doesn\u2019t shake so bad and the characters are interesting and have things to do, then it\u2019s pretty badass.\n- file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1105/re-ranker-msmarco/36.txt\n- Henry is just an average guy\u2026 An average guy who was blown to pieces, rebuilt as a cyborg and now has to tear his way through Russia to save his wife from a telekinetic madman who looks and sounds like an albino Tommy Wiseau.\n- file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1105/re-ranker-msmarco/18.txt\n- The film is not unlike that of a video game and the gaming industry as a whole has come a long way into embracing the first-person perspective.\n\nThe runtime for \"Hardcore Henry\" (2015) is mentioned in the file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1105/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt, which states that it's 1h 36m. \n\nTherefore, the output to the query \"The runtime of the film Hardcore (2015) is 90.0.\" would be:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document does not provide any information about a film titled \"Hardcore\" from 2015 with a runtime of 90 minutes. The document discusses a movie called \"Hardcore Henry,\" which has a different runtime (1h 36m) and director (Ilya Naishuller)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}